justfab.ca 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | JustFab

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy addresses how Just Fabulous, Inc., and its affiliated brands ("JustFab") collect and use information you provide. By visiting www.JustFab.com (this "Site"), and providing your information to us, you agree to accept the practices described in this privacy policy.

What Information Is Collected  
We group the collection of user information into two categories: personal, which is information identifiable to a specific member, and aggregate, which is general demographic information that does not identify any individual member. Personal information may include your name, email address, mailing address, credit card information and phone number. We may also collect certain demographic information such as your site preferences, age, gender, geographical location, language, time zone, income and education (some of the information we ask for may be optional). JustFab may use or disclose aggregate information for any purpose.

How We Use Your Information  
We collect personal information to make our services related to this Site ("Services") more rewarding for you to use, including billing, shipping and tracking your orders. If we have any questions or concerns regarding your order, we may use this information to contact you. We also use this information for internal purposes, such as studying our customers' preferences and improving the customers' experiences. We may also use your information to contact you for promotional purposes. We also may use this information to provide customer service to you. If you enter into a sweepstakes, contest, or similar promotion, we may use the information you provide to administer those activities. We may combine information about you with information from other sources in order to improve the quality of our services.

We also receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information, which is collected passively using various technologies, and cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. This Site may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers, and how our users use and interact with the Services. Also, in an ongoing effort to better understand and serve you, we often conduct research on customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the personal information and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. We may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with affiliates, agents and business partners, but this type of non-identifiable and aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our Services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

How is this Information Shared  
There are certain circumstances in which we may share your personal information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

  * We may share information about you with trusted third parties in order to improve your consumer experience. These third parties may contact you about products, services or promotions you may be interested in, or to otherwise improve your customer experience with this Site.
  * As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, your information may be part of the transferred assets.
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of JustFab, its users or the public.
  * As required by law, to comply with a judicial proceeding or court order, to exercise our rights, or to defend against any claims.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
This Site uses cookies and web beacons to gather aggregated, non-personally identifiable information in order to help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of this Site users have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. Such information may be shared with trusted third-parties but the information will not personally identify you. To the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information. As we develop this Site, we may gather additional information from you through the use of other technologies.

Cookie  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to collect anonymous information about how you use this Site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our Site, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave our Site. The cookies are not connected to your personal information. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of this Site's features.

Web Beacon  
Web beacons, or clear gifs, are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages. Web beacons help us better manage content on our Site by informing us what content is effective. We do not tie the information gathered by web beacons to your personal information.

Security  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you provide sensitive information (such as a credit card number), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of such information. If you have any questions about security on our Site, please contact us as indicated below.

Opting Out  
We may occasionally send you newsletters and emails regarding special offers, promotions, features and/or product updates. We may also communicate with you on behalf of third parties about special offers, promotions, features and/or product updates we think may be of interest to you, or you may have opted-in to receive newsletters or special promotions from one of our trusted third party providers. If you decide you do not wish to receive these communications, you may opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe link or by following the instructions included in the communication. Note however that as user of the Service you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to the Service, such as billing or service notifications.

Links to Other Sites  
This Site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy does not cover any information that you disclose to such sites or that they may collect. The privacy policies of these other sites may be significantly different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there. This Site may enable you to post comments, reviews and other information on publicly available areas of this Site. Any information you post in these areas of this Site will be available to all of our users, so please use caution in disclosing any personal information when you post such comments, reviews or other information.

Facebook  
You can log in to your Account using your Facebook account, or utilize your Facebook account to access and use the social features on this Site. In doing so, Facebook will ask your permission to share certain information from your Facebook account with this Site. This may include your first name, last name, gender, profile picture, list of friends, a link to your Facebook profile, likes, and other data that is part of your or your friends' Facebook profile(s). This information is collected by Facebook and is provided to us under the terms of Facebook's Privacy Policy. You can control the information that we receive from Facebook using the privacy settings in your Facebook account. If you use your Facebook account to access and use the social features on this Site, your Facebook user name and your Facebook profile picture will be shared with other users of this Site. Further, other users of this Site may be able to view your profile and shopping activity on this Site. 

You may choose to share your shopping activity on this Site with your friends on Facebook. A subset of your user activity on this Site, including your likes, purchases, wishlists and friends will automatically be shared to both your friends on Facebook and with your Facebook friends on this Site. Additionally, such activity will be visible to users on this Site who have a Facebook account but who might not be your friend on Facebook. The information you choose to share with your Facebook friends will be attributed to your Facebook account that was used to access this Site. Facebook's use of such information and any information it collects from your use of Facebook is governed by Facebook's Privacy Policy, JustFab has no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of Facebook that may be enabled within use of this Site. The use of information on this Site is governed by this Site's Privacy Policy. You understand and acknowledge that you have read and are familiar with this Site's Privacy Policy and Facebook's Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to share your activity on this Site with your friends on Facebook, you may adjust your sharing settings on this Site at any time to disable such sharing. You understand and acknowledge that if you adjust your settings to disable such sharing on Facebook, such activity may continue to be publicly available to other users on this Site, including users with Facebook accounts.

Updating or Deleting Your Online Account Information: You may update or correct your online account information at any time by logging into your account and navigating to the "My Account" page or by contacting us. You can also contact us by phone if you wish to deactivate your account, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

Children Under 13  
Children under 13 may view this Site, but they cannot make a purchase or provide any personal information. This Site is not designed for children and we do not wish to collect personal information from children under 13. If you register with us and we discover that you are under 13, we will delete your account. You must be 18 or over to purchase any products from this Site. If a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information online, we ask that a parent or guardian contact us.

Exclusion to this Privacy Policy  
This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to JustFab through this Site or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as review sections and forums (collectively, "Public Areas"), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, "Unsolicited Information"). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and JustFab shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution.

California Residents  
If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with us, you can request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information we have shared with third parties, for the third parties' direct marketing purposes, during the preceding calendar year. To request a notice, please submit your request to Just Fabulous, Inc., Attn: Legal Department, California Shine the Light Inquiry, 800 Apollo Drive, El Segundo, CA 90245.

U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Data Protection: JustFab recognizes that the European Union ("EU") has implemented omnibus data protection regimes established pursuant to the European Data Protection Directive (95/46/EC). Among other things, this law requires "adequate protection" for the transfer of certain individually identifiable data about individuals in EU member countries to JustFab's operations in the United States of America ("U.S."). JustFab complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of Personal Information from EU member countries. JustFab has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program and to view JustFab's certification, click here

Amendments or Modifications to this Policy  
We reserve the right to amend this policy at any time without prior notice. Notice of any change will be posted on this Site. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

Contact Us  
If you have any questions regarding the use of our site or privacy policy, please contact us at:

JustFab  
Attn: Legal Department/Privacy   
800 Apollo Drive  
El Segundo, CA 90245  
Or 1-866-337-0906
